http://www.dnronline.com/site/privacy.html

If you already are a subscriber, please
Log In.
Shenandoah County
Virginia (AP)
National (AP)
International (AP)
Shenandoah County
Virginia (AP)
National (AP)
International (AP)
Events
TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE AND PRIVACY POLICYThe Daily News-Record (“Daily News-Record”) offers this Web site, including all information, software, products and services available from the Web site or offered as part of or in conjunction with the Web site (the “Web site”), to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of all of the terms, conditions, policies and notices stated here. The Daily News-Record reserves the right to make changes to these Terms and Conditions immediately by posting the changed Terms and Conditions in this location. Your continued use of the Web site constitutes your agreement to all such terms, conditions and notices, and any changes to these Terms and Conditions made by the Daily News-Record. Accessing the Web site, in any manner, whether automated or otherwise, constitutes use of the Web site and your agreement to be bound by these Terms and Conditions.Personal, Noncommercial and Nontransferable UseYou agree that your access to the Web site, certain portions of which you may have paid to access, is for your personal, noncommercial and nontransferable use. You are not allowed to reproduce, forward, barter, resell, assign or otherwise transfer in any way your personal access rights. As a condition to your continued use of the Web site, you warrant to the Daily News-Record that you will not use the Web site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms and Conditions.No WarrantiesUSE THE WEB SITE AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE WEB SITE IS PROVIDED TO YOU “AS IS,” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. THE DAILY NEWS-RECORD MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT ANY CONTENT CONTAINED ON THE WEB SITE SATISFIES ANY APPLICABLE GOVERNMENT LAW, REGULATION OR REQUIREMENT. We do not make any representations, nor do we endorse the accuracy, completeness, timeliness or reliability of any advice, opinion, statement or other material or database displayed, uploaded or distributed by the Web site or available through links on the Web site. Neither Daily News-Record nor its employees, agents, third-party information providers, merchants, licensors or the like warrant that the Web site or its operation will be accurate, reliable, uninterrupted or error-free. There may be delays, omissions, interruptions and inaccuracies in the news, information or other materials available on the Web site. We are not responsible for the availability or content of other services that may be linked to the Web site. Although we intend to take reasonable steps to prevent the introduction of viruses, worms, “Trojan horses” or other destructive materials to the Web site, we do not guarantee or warrant that the Web site or materials that may be downloaded from the Web site do not contain such destructive features. We are not liable for any damages or harm attributable to such features. If you rely on the Web site and any materials available through the Web site, you do so solely at your own risk. No agent or representative has the authority to create any warranty regarding the Web site on behalf of Daily News-Record. The Daily News-Record reserves the right to change or discontinue at any time any aspect or feature of the Web site.Exclusion of LiabilityUNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES, INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE, SHALL DAILY NEWS-RECORD OR ANYONE ELSE INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING, STORING OR DISTRIBUTING THE WEB SITE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES AND EXPENSES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS, AND DAMAGES ARISING FROM LOST DATA OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH USE OF THE WEB SITE, DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEB SITE, OR FOR ANY INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEB SITE, WHETHER SUCH DAMAGES ARE BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. YOU SPECIFICALLY AGREE THAT NO LICENSOR, SUPPLIER OR INFORMATION PROVIDER TO DAILY NEWS-RECORD OR ITS AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES OR AGENTS, OR ANY OF THEIR SUCCESSORS OR ASSIGNS, SHALL HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY REASON OR UNDER ANY THEORY WHATSOEVER, BASED UPON THE INFORMATION PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE WEB SITE. YOU SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT WE ARE NOT LIABLE FOR ANY DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF ANY USER. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH THE WEB SITE, OR ANY MATERIALS, PRODUCTS, OR SERVICES ON THE WEBSITE, OR WITH ANY OF THE WEB SITE’S TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE WEB SITE. Because some states do not permit the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, some or all of the above limitation may not apply to you.IndemnificationYou agree to defend, indemnify and hold Daily News-Record, its officers, directors, affiliated companies, employees and agents, licensors and suppliers harmless from and against any and all claims, actions or demands, liabilities and settlements, including, without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees, resulting from, or alleged to result from, your use of the Web site, or any content, product or service offered through the Web site, or any content or information furnished by you to the Web site, in a manner that violates or is alleged to violate these Terms and Conditions. Daily News-Record shall provide notice to you of any such claim, suit or proceeding and shall reasonably cooperate with you, at your expense, in your defense of any such claim, suit or proceeding. We reserve the right to take over the exclusive defense of any claim for which we are entitled to indemnification. In such event, you shall provide us with such cooperation as is reasonably requested by us.Featured Links and AdvertisementsThe Web site may contain hyperlinks to web sites offered by parties other than Daily News-Record.Such hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only. The Daily News-Record does not control such other web sites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites; nor does Daily News-Record inclusion of hyperlinks to such web sites imply any endorsement of the material on such web sites or any association with their operators, including any web sites that may indicate a special relationship or partnership with Daily News-Record (such as co-branded pages or “powered by” or “in cooperation with” relationships). Unless otherwise specifically stated on the Web site, Daily News-Record does not endorse any product or service or make any representation regarding the reliability, quality or accuracy of any products or services featured in, or linked to, any advertisement, article or other content appearing on the Web site.Daily News-Record does not disclose personally identifiable information or unique identifiers to those responsible for the linked web sites. The linked web sites, however, may collect personal information from you that is not subject to Daily News-Record’s control. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policy of the web sites you may visit by linking from the Web site.Responsibility for Your User Name and PasswordTo use certain features on the Web site, you will need a user name and password, which you will receive through the Web site’s registration process. We reserve the right to reject or terminate the use of any user name that we deem offensive or inappropriate. In addition, we also reserve the right to terminate the use of any user name or account, or to deny access to the Web site or any features of the Web site, to anyone who violates these Terms and Conditions or who, in our sole judgment, interferes with the ability of others to enjoy the Web site or infringes on the rights of others. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account, and are responsible for all activities (whether by you or others) that occur under your password or account. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and to ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. We can not and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to protect your password or account information.Payment Obligation and Credit Card AuthorizationYou agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted during the registration process. Paying users authorize Daily News-Record’s payment processor(s) to charge the user’s credit card (or other approved facility) for the ongoing cost of access to certain portions of the Web site. Payment for the appropriate services will be made by automatic debit to the user’s credit card (or other approved facility). Paying users will be automatically renewed for a term equal to the original term upon expiration of the then-current term, and continually thereafter, unless the user terminates his or her account online prior to the renewal date pursuant to the process set forth below. You may not assign or transfer your account to any other individual or entity. You must have reached the age of majority in your jurisdiction in order to register.Payment must be made by a major credit card, checking account or phone charge accepted by Daily News-Record’s payment processor(s). The billing period ends each term on the anniversary of your activation date. If Daily News-Record does not receive payment from the credit card issuer or its agent, you agree to pay all amounts due upon demand by Daily News-Record. Your card issuer agreement governs your use of your designated card, and you must refer to that agreement and not these Terms and Conditions to determine your rights and liabilities as a cardholder. YOU, AND NOT DAILY NEWS-RECORD, ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR PAYING ANY AMOUNTS BILLED TO YOUR CREDIT CARD BY A THIRD PARTY WHICH WERE NOT AUTHORIZED BY YOU.DAILY NEWS-RECORD RESERVES THE RIGHT, AT ANY TIME, TO CHANGE ITS FEES AND BILLING METHODS, INCLUDING THE ADDITION OF SUPPLEMENTAL FEES OR SEPARATE CHARGES FOR CONTENT OR SERVICES PROVIDED BY DAILY NEWS-RECORD, EFFECTIVE THIRTY (30) DAYS AFTER AN ONLINE POSTING AT DAILY NEWS-RECORD. DAILY NEWS-RECORD MAY ADDITIONALLY PROVIDE NOTICE OF BILLING CHANGES VIA E-MAIL. IF ANY SUCH CHANGE IS UNACCEPTABLE TO YOU, YOU MAY TERMINATE YOUR ACCOUNT, AS PROVIDED BELOW. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF YOUR ACCOUNT FOLLOWING THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF A CHANGE TO SUCH FEES AND BILLING METHODS SHALL CONSTITUTE YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH CHANGE.You must promptly inform Daily News-Record of any of the following: changes in the expiration date of any credit card used in connection with your account; changes in home or billing address; and apparent breaches of security, such as loss, theft or unauthorized disclosure or use of an account or password. Until Daily News-Record is notified by e-mail of a breach in security, the user will remain liable for any unauthorized use of his or her account, and for any charges that accrued to his or her account.Cancellation of AccountYou may terminate your account by contacting Daily News-Record at any time. When termination is requested, your credit card (or other approved facility) will not be automatically renewed and access will be terminated on the expiration date. Termination of your account shall not relieve you of any obligations to pay accrued charges, including any prorated charges accrued for the billing cycle during which your account is terminated.Software Available on Web SiteAny software that is made available to download from the Web site is the copyrighted work of Daily News-Record and/or its suppliers. Your use of the software is governed by the terms of the end user license agreement, if any, that accompanies or is included with the software. You may not install or use any software without first agreeing to the terms of such end user license agreement. For any software not accompanied by an end user license agreement, Daily News-Record hereby grants to you a personal, nontransferable, non-sublicensable license to use the software for viewing and other purposes within the scope of use of such software anticipated by Daily News-Record in accordance with these Terms and Conditions, and for no other purpose. Any such software is provided to you subject to the warranty and liability exclusions set forth in these Terms and Conditions.CopyrightExcept for material in the public domain under United States copyright law, all material contained on the Web site (including all software, HTML code, Java applets, Active X controls and other code) is protected by United States and foreign copyright laws. Except as otherwise expressly provided in these Terms and Conditions, you may not copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, modify, rewrite, upload, post, exploit, create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any material contained on the Web site without the prior consent of the copyright owner. None of the material contained on the Web site may be reverse-engineered, disassembled, decompiled, transcribed, stored in a retrieval system, translated into any language or computer language, retransmitted in any form or by any means (electronic, mechanical, photo reproduction, recordation or otherwise), resold or redistributed without the prior written consent of Daily News-Record. You may not create hyperlinks to the content on the Web site, distribute any part of the Web site over any network, including a local area network, nor sell or offer it for sale. In addition, these files may not be used to construct any kind of database. Under no circumstances may you “frame” the Web site or any of its content or copy portions of the Web site to a server, except as part of an Internet service provider’s incidental caching of pages. Violation of this provision may result in severe civil and criminal penalties.You may make single copies of materials displayed on the Web site for your own personal and noncommercial use only, provided any copies include the copyright and other notices displayed with the materials on the Web site. You may not distribute such copies to others, whether or not for a charge or other consideration, without prior written permission from Daily News-Record or the copyright owner of the copied material. Requests to reproduce materials on the Web site for distribution or other purposes should be mailed to:The Daily News-RecordAttn: Peter YatesP.O. Box 193Harrisonburg, VA 22803phone: (540) 574-6200fax: (540) 574-6299e-mail: pyates@dnronline.com Trademarks“The Daily News-Record” is a trademark of Rockingham Publishing Co., Inc., and is protected by state and federal trademark laws. Other trademarks appear on the Web site with permission from their respective owners. Your unauthorized use of trademarks appearing on the Web site may constitute trademark infringement, which could subject you to substantial civil penalties.Termination of PrivilegesDaily News-Record reserves the right to terminate your privilege of using all or any portion of the Web site if you breach any of these Terms and Conditions. If Daily News-Record receives notice or otherwise discovers that you have posted material that infringes another party’s copyright or trademark rights or violates another party’s rights of privacy or publicity, Daily News-Record may terminate your access to the Web site, including all of your privileges or accounts that you may have established in connection with the Web site. You acknowledge that any fees you may have paid to access certain portions of the Web site are not refundable, in whole or part, upon such termination.Copyright InfringementDaily News-Record will not tolerate copyright infringement of any kind. Daily News-Record does not, however, monitor user-submitted materials for copyright infringement. If you believe that any material on the Web site infringes your copyright, you may seek to have the material removed by sending Daily News-Record notice that includes all of the following information:your full name, address and telephone number;your e-mail address;identification of the copyrighted work(s) that you believe is being infringed;identification of the infringing material and information sufficient for Daily News-Record to locate the material;your statement of good faith belief that (a) the material infringes your copyrights, (b) the information provided in the notice is accurate, and (c) under penalty of perjury, you are authorized to act for the copyright owner; andyour physical or electronic signature. Direct such notice to Daily News-Record’s designated agent for receiving copyright infringement notices:Rockingham Publishing Co., Inc.Peter Yates, Editor and General ManagerP.O. Box 193Harrisonburg, VA 22803phone: (540) 574-6200fax: (540) 574-6299e-mail: pyates@dnronline.com Any personal information you provide in your notice will be used only for purposes related to your notice. Upon receipt of notice complying with the above requirements, Daily News-Record will act to remove infringing materials and, if applicable, send notice to the user that posted such materials on the Web site.If Daily News-Record removes materials posted by you as a user due to alleged copyright infringement, you may seek to have the materials reinstated by notifying Daily News-Record’s designated agent in writing and including the following information:your full name, address and telephone numberyour e-mail addressidentification of the material that has been removed or to which access has been disabled, including its location before it was removed or disabledyour statement under penalty of perjury that you have a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or misidentification of the materialyour statement consenting to the jurisdiction of the Federal District Court for the district in which your address is located, or, if you reside outside of the United States, for the Western District of Virginia (where Daily News-Record may be found), and that you will accept service of process from the person who provided notice of copyright infringement or from such person’s agentyour physical or electronic signature Upon receipt of a notice meeting the above requirements, Daily News-Record will send a copy of the notice to the copyright owner who initially claimed copyright infringement. Within 10 to 14 days following receipt of the notice, Daily News-Record will replace or enable access to the removed material unless Daily News-Record receives notice from the copyright owner who submitted the first notification that it has filed an action seeking a court order to restrain the user that posted the materials from engaging in infringing activity. Please note that parties who misrepresent that materials are infringing or were removed by mistake or misidentification are subject to substantial civil liability to Daily News-Record and/or the copyright owner or Web site user.User ContentDaily News-Record may allow you to upload, post, transmit or otherwise provide content to the Web site, including, but not limited to, photos, video, audio, comments, articles, blogs, forums and any other such communication in which you provide content to the Web site (“User Content”). You agree that you are solely responsible for any communications and any content provided through your account.Rules Governing User Content. In consideration for being allowed to post or contribute content, you agree that your failure to abide by the following rules in using the Web site shall constitute a material breach of these Terms and Conditions:Do not disrespect the privacy and views of others, or use the Web site to stalk or harass another;Do not use or provide User Content for commercial purposes, including but not limited to the promotion of any specific goods or services;Do not provide User Content that is harmful to minors in any way;Do not provide obscene, profane, sexually explicit, libelous, slanderous, defamatory, harmful, threatening, illegal or knowingly false User Content;Do not provide User Content containing expressions of bigotry, racism or hate;Do not provide User Content encouraging conduct that may constitute or contribute to a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability or violate any national, state or local law, regulation or authority;Do not impersonate another person, or permit any other person or entity to use your identification to post or view User Content;Do not provide User Content that infringes on the copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret or other intellectual property rights of others;Do not provide User Content that violates the privacy or publicity rights of others;Do not provide User Content that supports or provides resources to any organization(s) designated by the United States government as a foreign terrorist organization pursuant to section 219 of the Immigration and Nationality Act, as amended; andDo not provide User Content containing malicious code, including but not limited to computer viruses, Trojan horses, or other programs designed to disrupt, damage or restrict the use of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment. Respect the Intellectual Property Rights of Others. You may not post or transmit content belonging to any person or party other than yourself, without the prior written consent of such owner. Simply because material is available on the Internet does not mean it is in the public domain. The vast majority of materials on the Internet are protected by copyright and trademark laws. Daily News-Record shall have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor any User Content areas of the Web site to determine compliance with these Terms and Conditions and any other operating rules that may be established by Daily News-Record from time to time.Daily News-Record’s Right to Remove User Content. Daily News-Record does not assume any responsibility for the consequences of any user-generated or contributed content on the Web site. If notified by a user of communications that are alleged not to conform to the rules set forth herein, Daily News-Record may investigate the allegation and determine in its sole discretion to remove or request the removal of the communications. Daily News-Record reserves the right to remove communications that fail to conform to these Terms and Conditions. In addition, Daily News-Record reserves the right (but is not obligated) to delete any User Content posted on the Web site, regardless of whether such communications violate these Terms and Conditions.Daily News-Record’s Right to Use User Content. Daily News-Record reserves the right to record, re-purpose or re-publish User Content on its Web site, newspapers, broadcast stations or other publishing forums. By posting User Content, you are granting to Daily News-Record and its licensees a worldwide, royalty-free, perpetual, non-exclusive and irrevocable right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, perform and display any posting by you (in whole or in part) and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media or technology now known or hereafter developed.Responsibility for User Content. You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Daily News-Record and its officers, directors, affiliated companies, employees, agents, licensors and suppliers, from and against any and all claims, actions or demands, liabilities and settlements, including, without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees, resulting from, or alleged to result from, your use of any User-generated or contributed content or use by others of any User-generated or contributed content with respect to you, including, without limitation, any claim of libel, defamation, harassment, violation of rights of privacy or publicity, loss of service or infringement of intellectual property or other rights, or violation of these Terms and Conditions.NOTE TO USERS. Daily News-Record does not represent or guarantee the truthfulness, accuracy or reliability of any User Content or endorse any opinions expressed by such users. ANY RELIANCE UPON USER CONTENT IS AT YOUR OWN RISK.Termination of PrivilegesDaily News-Record reserves the right to terminate your privilege of using all or any portion of the Web site if you breach any of these Terms and Conditions. If Daily News-Record receives notice or otherwise discovers that you have posted material that infringes another party’s copyright or trademark rights or violates another party’s rights of privacy or publicity, Daily News-Record may terminate your access to the Web site, including all of your privileges or accounts that you may have established in connection with the Web site. In the event that Daily News-Record terminates your access to the Web site, you will continue to be bound by these Terms and Conditions as in effect as of the date of such termination.GeneralThese Terms and Conditions (including the privacy policy hereinafter set forth, which shall be deemed to be a part of these Terms and Conditions) constitute the entire agreement and understanding between you and Daily News-Record with respect to use of the Web site, superseding all prior or contemporaneous communications and/or proposals. These Terms and Conditions also are severable, and in the event any provision is determined to be invalid or unenforceable, such invalidity or unenforceability shall not in any way affect the validity or enforceability of the remaining provisions. Daily News-Record reserves the right to make changes to these Terms and Conditions immediately by posting the changed Terms and Conditions in this location. By continuing to use the Web site, you are agreeing to all changes made by Daily News-Record. A printed version of these Terms and Conditions shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to use of the Web site to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form.JurisdictionThe Web site is controlled and operated by Daily News-Record from its principal office in the Commonwealth of Virginia, United States of America. Daily News-Record makes no representation that materials on the Web site are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access the Web site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. The Web site is not intended to subject Daily News-Record to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than the Commonwealth of Virginia and the United States of America.PRIVACY POLICYFor each visitor to the Web site, Daily News-Record’s servers automatically collect information about which pages are visited and the domain name of visitors. This information is used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and for Web site traffic audits. We also provide this information (as well as information from third-party market researchers) about our users on an aggregated, anonymous basis to our advertisers.Daily News-Record may place a “cookie” on the browser of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. A cookie may be used to tell when your computer has contacted the Web site. Daily News-Record uses the information for editorial purposes and for other purposes such as delivery of features and advertisements, so Daily News-Record can customize delivery of information to you without compromising privacy. For example, cookies may be used to ensure that you will not see the same banner advertisement too often in a single session.Daily News-Record may, in the course of providing services through its Web site, ask you to disclose voluntarily certain information about yourself. This could include information that identifies you or your household. Any information in Daily News-Record’s possession solely as a result of your use of the Web site and that is associated with you or your household is considered “Personal Information.” It consists of both information supplied by you (e.g. name, address, telephone number and e-mail address) and information collected about how you use the Web site (e.g. the fact that you have bought merchandise through the Web site). “Personal Information” does not include statistical data about large numbers of users, none of whom are identifiable, nor does it include information that you have posted for public view on the Web site or otherwise publicly disclosed.Like many other commercial sites, the Web site may utilize an electronic file called a web beacon to count users who have visited a page or recognize users by accessing certain cookies. The Web site and/or the web sites of advertisers and merchants with which we have a relationship may use web beacons (a) for auditing purposes and to collect information from the web sites of certain advertisers or merchants; and (b) to report anonymous individual and/or aggregate information about our users from such advertisers or merchants. Aggregate information may include demographic and usage information. No personally identifiable information about you is shared with such advertisers or merchants. You may choose to opt-out by contacting us in accordance with the information set forth at the bottom of this privacy policy.Daily News-Record uses Personal Information only for purposes necessary to provide the Web site and other products and services to you. These purposes are:to process requests or orders placed with advertisers or merchants;to perform such normal business operations as billing, collecting and accounting;to personalize and publicize the Web site based on your interests, including making you aware of editorial features, advertisements and commercial items; andto investigate complaints and to protect the Web site and Daily News-Record, its readers and employees as provided by law or in case of emergency, as determined by legal counsel for Daily News-Record. Except as necessary to process your requests or orders placed with advertisers or merchants featured on the Web site, Daily News-Record does not rent, sell, barter or give away any lists containing Personal Information for use by any outside company. Daily News-Record also respects the privacy of data on your personal computer and does not access, read, upload or store data contained in or derived from your private files without your authorization.LinksThe Web site contains links to other sites. Daily News-Record is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites, including any sites that may indicate a special relationship or partnership with Daily News-Record (such as co-branded pages or “powered by” or “in cooperation with” relationships). Daily News-Record does not disclose personally identifiable information or unique identifiers to those responsible for the linked sites. The linked sites, however, may collect personal information from you that is not subject to Daily News-Record’s control. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policy of the sites you may visit by linking from the Web site.Opt Out ProceduresYou may always opt out of receiving future mailings or other information from Daily News-Record. If the mailing does not have an e-mail cancellation form, send us an e-mail detailing the type of information that you no longer desire to receive.Children’s PrivacyThe following additional terms, conditions and notices apply to use of the Web site by children under the age of 13 years whenever Daily News-Record becomes aware that a user is in that age range:Users under 13 years of age may not submit or post information on the Web site without the consent of the user’s parent or legal guardian. Prior to collecting any personal information about a child under 13, Daily News-Record makes reasonable efforts to obtain consent from the child’s parent after informing the parent about the types of information Daily News-Record will collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances it will be disclosed.Although Daily News-Record will apply these children’s terms and conditions whenever it becomes aware that a user who submits Personal Information is less than 13 years old, no method is foolproof. Daily News-Record strongly encourages parents and guardians to supervise their children’s online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools also can prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission.“Personal information” collected from children may include any of the information defined above as “Personal Information” with respect to general users of the Web site and may be used by Daily News-Record for the same purposes. Except as necessary to process a child’s requests or orders placed with advertisers or merchants featured on the Web site, Daily News-Record does not rent, sell, barter or give away any lists containing a child’s Personal Information for use by any outside company.If a child enters a game, contest or other activity sponsored by Daily News-Record on the Web site, the child may be required by Daily News-Record to provide the minimum Personal Information reasonably necessary for the child to participate in such activity.A child’s parent or legal guardian may request Daily News-Record to provide a description of the Personal Information that Daily News-Record has collected from the child, as well as instruct Daily News-Record to cease further use, maintenance and collection of Personal Information from the child.If a child voluntarily discloses his or her name, e-mail address or other personally-identifying information on chat areas, bulletin boards or other forums or public posting areas, such disclosures may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. GeneralThese Terms and Conditions constitute the entire agreement and understanding between you and Daily News-Record with respect to use of the Web site, superseding all prior or contemporaneous communications and/or proposals. Daily News-Record reserves the right to make changes to these Terms and Conditions immediately by posting the changed Terms and Conditions in this location. By continuing to use the Web site, you are agreeing to all changes made by Daily News-Record. A printed version of these Terms and Conditions shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to use of the Web site to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form.The Web site is controlled and operated by Daily News-Record from its principal office in the Commonwealth of Virginia, United States of America. Daily News-Record makes no representation that materials on the Web site are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access the Web site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. The Web site is not intended to subject Daily News-Record to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than the Commonwealth of Virginia and the United States of America.AP News RegistryThis Web site uses services provided by AP News Registry. AP News Registry collects content usage information and may use cookies in conjunction with this activity. Your continued readership of the Site means you accept the privacy policy of the AP News Registry. Please refer to the AP News Registry privacy policy at http://www.apnewsregistry.com/privacycenter/servicepolicy.aspx for further information.Contacting UsIf you have any questions about these Terms and Conditions, the practices of the Web site, or your dealings with Daily News-Record, you may contact us at:The Daily News-RecordAttn: Peter YatesP.O. Box 193Harrisonburg, VA 22803phone: (540) 574-6200fax: (540) 574-6299e-mail: pyates@dnronline.com
Coronavirus Coverage Free To Read
To help keep the community informed about critical developments during the current coronavirus crisis, The Daily News-Record has temporarily opened free access to all articles related to the COVID-19 pandemic and its local, regional and national impacts.
Success! An email has been sent to
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
News Updates
Sign up to stay up to date with our daily Headlines and COVID-19 Updates newsletters.
Please enter a valid email address.
Sign up
Manage your lists
Most Popular Articles
Articles
ArticlesSorry, there are no recent results for popular articles.
“Stories on Two Feet: Kimberlea Daggy”
© Copyright 2020 Daily News-Record, 231 S. Liberty St. Harrisonburg, VA | Terms & Conditions - Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
